What's up, man?
LOL!
Oh, she's amazing.
There's moldy rose, moldy rose
Two moldy roses.
Laughing.
Let's catch our breath.
I got it.
Did it? Oh, my God. - Oh, my God.
You think it'll work?
That's so sweet.
You're so cute!
What? You're so tongue-tied.
LOL!
Hello, Morita san
Hello Masumoto san
You're dazzling
It's so bright
It makes my eyes dizzy
Forgive me
It's outside
Outside.
What is this place?
This is Gunma Safari Park!
We love animals.
We love animals and we wanted to go there!
We promised ourselves once that we would go there privately.
We were so excited to be able to come with this project.
We are very happy to be able to come with this project.
I'm so happy!
The cherry blossoms are in full bloom
It's so beautiful.
It's so bright over here.
This way, this way...
Cherry blossoms!
I'm so happy to be here on such a beautiful day like this.
I'm so happy!
I'm looking forward to seeing lots of animals!
Let's get started!
Let's go!
Go!
Good morning.
Good morning. Good morning.
We're on a private tour today.
Yes, ma'am.
P.S. Today we'd like to show you two
Takatani and...
Takatani-san...
Takatani-san... should I move you?
Should we do it together?
I don't know.
Ms. Takatani?
Ms. Takatani.
How old are you, Ms. Takatani?
I'm 21.
I'm 22.
Twenty-two.
Do you have any hobbies?
Hobbies?
I like outdoor activities.
You're really good at keeping your bangs in place.
What are you talking about?
What's this?
Oh my God!
I see a giraffe!
Where, where, where, where?
The giraffe you see on the right is called an amimekirin.
Amime giraffe.
This little guy's name is...
Because he was born in the summer
He is called Natsugoro.
Natsugoro
When you let him go from the net
If you hold it a little...
It's so long! Amazing!
If you bring it a little closer...
Wow, wow, wow, you're entangling it.
Yes, you're right, twirl it.
The color is amazing.
Beautiful eyelashes.
Long neck.
He has a long neck bone.
Neck bone.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I'm sorry, I interrupted you.
How many neck bones are there?
We have seven bones in our neck, just like you and me.
That's right.
Inoue has one more than a giraffe.
Certainly.
Inoue has one more.
The Inoue family has been the head of the family for generations.
Like grandma has one too.
Why?
Oh, there it is!
So cute!
Open this window.
I'll close this window.
Cute.
Natsugoro's cute.
You already know it's him, don't you?
So close.
Very close.
It's a little bumpy.
It's shaking a little.
That's cute.
Whoa.
Oh, wow.
Oh, man.
Bummer.
Yay! Yay! Yay!
Wow! Amazing! Fun!
More, more, more, Mr. Takai!
I'd like to even things out a bit.
Oh, I'm sorry, I don't know what to do.
What should we do?
Eat up!
So cute!
That's a nice sprout.
There he is. One of them.
He's here.
I'm so glad. Um...
Cute.
Isn't he big?
This one's a big boy. He's so big, he's so big.
Fireworks.
Hey, boss.
Rina Matsuda?
America Zone
Coming into the America Zone.
Here's where it shakes again.
Yay!
Have you been drinking?
Oh, no.
I'm drinking my mother's milk.
Bison.
I've heard that one before.
Eat.
Oh, my God.
You're really going all out, aren't you, baby?
Yes, he is.
Cool.
Ooh.
Yay.
That's a lot of breath.
Sniff, sniff, sniff.
Let's sniff, sniff, sniff, sniff, sniff!
I got it.
Did you get it?
Nice flower arrangement.
Only Barbata's bottom teeth.
Is that so?
It's just a tooth in the back.
You're sniffling.
Your hair sways with your breath.
I didn't know it was that bad.
Yes, it does.
What do you usually say?
Thank you for your hard work.
You're so cute! So cute! Dull eyes.
I'd like to move on.
I'm modeling this bison and a certain Disney character.
It's out on Advice Tik.
It took me a second to figure it out.
Surely not?
Beauty and the Beast.
That's right.
You know what I mean?
I thought I'd seen something like that before.
The Beast was modeled after this bison.
That's right.
What does that mean? What does that mean?
What does that mean?
Look at this.
Beauty and the Beast.
Turn around.
What does that mean?
The live-action Beauty and the Beast.
Oh, my God.
Look at this.
Is that what you're saying?
That's what you're saying.
That's so sweet.
You're a dick.
Bye-bye, my prince.
Bye-bye.
Bye-bye, Son.
We went to a place called Walking Safari Zone
Walking Safari Zone
Once there, you can get out of the car.
You can see the park and feed the lions and white tigers.
I love lions!
I'd like to take you there, and I'll take you there.
Cat?
Cats?
Wildcats.
Wildcats... how cool is that?
Is that okay?
Yes, and we also have a white tiger and a lion back there.
Oh, you want the lion? No, I'm good with either one.
You want the lion?
Either one would be fine.
Well, just open it up already.
It's open!
All the way down to the back of the net.
It's coming. It's coming.
They're coming.
It's so close! It's so close!
He's coming so slowly.
He looks sleepy.
Here he comes. Here he comes.
He's so cute! Can we go?
He's so sweet.
You're so cute!
He's got a little tongue.
That's a big cat.
He's adorable.
Thank you.
He's so cute!
I've never seen one this close before.
It's a cat! I've never seen a tail like that before.
It's not the kind of tail I imagined.
It's so cute!
Oh, wow.
Oh, my God, there's so many of them.
They're laying down. Hello.
Oh, I was so hungry.
GODS.
You're so cool.
You take your time.
That's so sweet.
I can't sleep through the night.
Cool, cool, cool.
He's so cute.
You're so cute when you sleep.
Where does he sleep?
Your face is so cute.
Can I get a close-up?
He's so cute.
Do you want just one of these?
I don't think so.
It's so cute.
Cute little head!
It's so cute!
It's too cute.
Oh, my gosh!
You're a cute little guy.
You're so deft.
He's got his face all rolled up.
Oh, my gosh!
He's moving so fast.
He's crossing his legs.
He's on his knees.
He's moving really, really fast.
He's moving sideways.
This is amazing.
That's the spirit of service!
Amazing.
Don't push yourself too hard.
She's a hard worker.
I bet you're good at it.
She's good.
She's amazing.
She's not a one-trick pony.
I want another one.
Did you get it?
I think I got it.
That's so awesome.
I want it for a friend.
One more time.
Okay, okay, okay.
She's so cute.
He's so cute.
She's so cute!
The information of this girl is
Here it is!
Maki Makuzaru
I'd like to give this kid's goat
We hope you will give it to him!
Thank you very much
I'll take it.
Hey...
You're not waiting for me?
I'm waiting.
There are two more goats in the back.
Any of them will do.
Which one do you want?
It's a tiebreaker.
Who wants it?
He's gonna want it.
He's cute.
I'm gonna give it to her.
That's good.
It's good.
I'm sorry. It's on the side.
I took it.
One egg.
He took the egg and the egg.
Thank you very much.
He took it?
And he took it all for himself.
Give me that.
Sylie, I screwed up.
Ouch.
Wait, he's so cute! He's doing the gas pedal!
He's so cute! Up, up, up!
Up, up, up! So cute!
I'm glad you got it.
So cute.
Okay, that's the second half of the show.
I'd like to go to the Asian zone and the mouge zone.
Now, on the right, you see the dromedary brachyura.
Take it, take it, take it!
I'm so fluffy too!
I'm totally fluffy!
They live in a very small area, so their eyelashes are very long.
It's true!
Maybe they're protecting their eyes from the sand.
They can even close their nostrils by themselves!
Next is the lion floor.
The lion
My favorite lion.
All the lions out there are now male lions.
Usually the males are
Outside again.
He's so cute.
He's putting his hand down.
Hands? Floating?
Oh, my God!
You're sleeping with your hands in the air.
That's what he does.
It's funny the way she sleeps.
You know what Maya?
What about her?
Open up.
Oh, he's awake.
She's got a sleeping habit.
He's cute.
Her legs are in a weird position.
Cross your legs like you're a person.
Left side and rhinoceros rhinoceros.
So cute.
Wow, the antlers.
They're so cute.
Their eyes are so low.
You mean they have wide foreheads?
Yes, that's right.
Wide forehead.
I like it here.
Where is it?
The meat on your leg.
I want to put my hand there.
I'd love to put my hand there.
Why do you like rhinos?
I went to the zoo.
And there was this one rhino.
He was so cute.
Love at first sight?
This way out the front.
And that's the end of our private tour.
Thank you very much.
The animals were so cute.
They were so cute.
It's good to see you.
Savannah Restaurant
I'm so excited!
Your food has arrived!
Thank you very much.
What did you have? I'm having bunny curry.
Too cute. I like sweet curry.
I see.
It came with a cute bunny and a toy.
A cute little pout? That's right.
I had an omelette. An omelette?
It's so delicious! You can enjoy both the black and white flavors.
And I challenged us...
What do you think this is? Morita san
This is crocodile Crocodile
In other words, crocodile meat Have you ever had it?
No, I've never had crocodile meat, I'll have some
Bon appétit!
At zoos and amusement parks, these food places...
I like them so much I go there even if I'm not hungry.
I know, I know. It's delicious. I love the atmosphere.
It's good. It's good. It's good.
What's this? It's so good.
Looks good. Yeah.
You want an animal? I'd love to have an animal.
What would you like?
I'm torn between a parakeet and a turtle.
But I'm pretty sure either one. Really?
You didn't buy one when you were at home?
I bought one when I was at home.
What? What?
But when you were little, you bought bunnies and stuff.
Yes, I did.
English, parakeets and dogs.
So I guess you like animals.
Yeah.
I wonder if the colors are similar...
There's a whitish part and a...
Yes, there are two kinds.
There's a part that changes.
Let's call it white.
On the contrary, it's black.
It's hard.
No, it's too hard.
Bon appétit!
I'm scared.
Oh, Yuki.
Pukka!
It's so good!
It tastes familiar.
Yes, I know it.
What does it resemble?
It's black.
It's not a film in my mouth.
It's hard.
Is that a joke?
Is it hard?
Is gravel hard?
Oh, is alligator meat hard?
Not at all.
Oh, my God, he said it's hard.
Not at all?
It's so hard, it's black.
Put your hands together and thank you for the food.
Thank you very much.
The alligator meat was delicious.
It was chewy and delicious.
You ate so beautifully.
Yes, I ate a lot.
Rabbit.
Rabbit Square
Oh, bunny.
Can I touch the sand and sugar?
You can only touch the inside of its mouth.
If you put your hand in front of your mouth and bite it...
Be careful.
Oh, are you okay now?
Oh, you're so cute.
So fluffy!
Fluffy
It's so cute.
Is it good? I'm losing so much hair.
You're not bringing it to the location?
I can bring it.
It's so white.
It's early.
Take it, take it, take it.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go!
That's good.
Get in the tube.
Tubes?
Capybaras.
Wait for the capybaras.
So cute!
I'll be waiting for you, Mr. Capybara.
Waiting for you.
Kapibara
Kabibara is...
Two Kabibaras.
Two Kabibaras
Bon appétit!
Wow!
What a surprise!
This one's...
This girl's feet are rough.
Oh, no...
Please lift up her legs only.
Heh...
That's great.
That's a great sound!
Kids will cry.
Kids are gonna cry.
Oh, shit.
Oh, wait, I'll come back.
Oh, my God!
You scared me.
Oh, my God.
Can I lift this?
Can I put this one up, too?
You scared the shit out of me.
You too.
You want one too?
Oh, my God, you're amazing.
You scared me.
I don't know if you can even hear how loud it is.
It's amazing, isn't it?
It's amazing.
Oh, my God!
It's gonna break the horn.
That was amazing!
You scared the shit out of me.
I still want it.
You still want it.
Heh.
Yes, ma'am.
Animal and honest.
Yes, yes, yes, yes.
The capybara will be a good girl and wait for you.
Yes, yes.
Hey, capybara.
This one eats this one and this one eats that one.
Yes, cute.
Scary, scary, scary. Here it comes, here it comes, here it comes.
Pygmy goats.
You got it.
Tabba.
Taba.
Lavishly.
Oh, my God. Isn't he cute?
You're so cute.
So cute.
Let's go to our favorite gift shop.
Yeah, let's go.
We'll definitely buy something.
And every time we go to the zoo, our favorite animal changes.
I buy something from a different animal every time.
I know, I know.
I'm so happy.
Who's today's MVP?
I already have an MVP.
Who's there?
White Tiger. You're in love.
He's so cute.
We're sold out!
Oh, there's a baby!
Wait, there's a baby!
The kid's cute.
I wish I had one.
Koho, can I show you something?
Look at this.
Wait, that's so cute!
It's so cute!
Yes, it is.
Yes!
I can use this for everyday!
It's cute!
But aren't you wearing a Nikomimi cap?
It's totally Macha, but...
Hey...
Yes, ma'am.
Yes, yes.
I went to the gift shop.
Cookies? Crunch chocolate.
So cute! I bought it because of the rhinoceros face.
It's so cute!
And an elephant magnet!
I also bought this cute little bunny that looks so cute when it's on your lap.
How were the animals? They were so cute and it was just like a normal holiday.
I'd like to go back to the animals again. I'd like to go back to the fish and the animal series.
I'd like to go again. Thank you very much.